mymostwanted.com 2011-12-31

# My Most Wanted Celebs - MyMostWanted.Com - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy will answer your questions regarding our privacy policies.  
By using and accessing the web sites where this Privacy Policy is located, you are accepting the terms and conditions of such Privacy Policy.  
Additional protections for children under the age of 13 who visit our site are detailed under the title of [MMW Children's Online Privacy Policy](http://www.mymostwanted.com/privacyp-children.php). 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

**Security**  
We protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of the personal information we collect. This information is maintained securely and only those people who require access may see this information. Even for newsletter subscribers, we only gather your e-mail address and do not share it with any other parties. The information gathered there and in our forum is kept secure.

**Links**  
Our site provides links to other sites. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users. We advise you to check their privacy policies as well. 

**Q.** What types of information do we collect?  
**A.** We do not collect personal information from anyone unless they register to participate on the website's Forum/Gallery. The only information we collect during our registration process is a member name, password, e-mail address, and birth date. We collect birth dates to validate the ages of our members, including children. We do not collect any other personally identifiable information during our registration process. 

**Q.** How do we use and share the personally identifiable information?   
**A.** Personal information may be disclosed in the course of participation in certain interactive features such as the forum. We do not share any information with any other third parties unless the disclosure is reasonably necessary: to comply with law, including, for example, comply with a court order or subpoena; to enforce our [Terms of Use](http://www.mymostwanted.com/termsofuse.php), or Site Rules; or to protect the safety and security of our visitors and our Web site. 

**Q.** How can you change or delete personally identifiable information?   
**A.** You can access, change, or delete the personal information that we have collected by logging in to your account and changing your profile information.

**Q.** How will we notify you if our Privacy Policy changes?  
**A.** We may amend our Privacy Policy at any time. We will provide notice on the site of any material changes in the way we intend to collect, use, and/or share personal information. We will apply material changes in our Privacy Policy only in conformance with applicable law, including any applicable provisions of COPPA that require parental consent.

**Q.** Are there other Terms of Use.   
**A.** Use of the mymostwanted.com site is governed by the "[Terms of Use](http://www.mymostwanted.com/termsofuse.php)" posted at the bottom of the mymostwanted.com site pages.  The [Terms of Use](http://www.mymostwanted.com/termsofuse.php) contain important provisions governing your and our rights including acceptable conduct on the mymostwanted.com site, intellectual property rights (for example, our right to use information, content and materials submitted to us by you) and other rights available to you, and us.  We ask that you read the [Terms of Use](http://www.mymostwanted.com/termsofuse.php) and ensure that you understand them.  If you do not want to be bound by these terms, do not register. 

**Q.** Who do visitors contact with questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy?   
**A.** If you need further assistance, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments. [Click Here](http://www.mymostwanted.com/contactus.php) to contact us.

**Q.** How do I contact mymostwanted?  
**A.** Please contact us at:

E-Mail: [Click Here](http://www.mymostwanted.com/contactus.php)

Telephone or fax: 231 744 4175

Mail: MMW, PO Box 0456 Muskegon, MI 49443-0456
